Miscellaneous Art Exhibition Catalog Collection
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: G-I, Series 3:
  - Henry Reinhardt & Son, 565 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Contemporary American Landscape, December 2-20, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Sculpture - A Plastic History of the War by Jo Davidson, April-May 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Hotel Bossert, Brooklyn, N.Y. (Box 3)
    - James Weiland, January 15-February 28 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Howard Young Galleries, 620 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - [Invitation] Exhibition of paintings from the estate of the late Potter Palmer of Chicago, October 9-28, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Catalogue of Paintings From the Estate of the Late Potter Palmer, October 9-28, 1922 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Annual Exhibition of Paintings by the Taos Society of Artists, November 4-18, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Hugo Gallery, 26 East 55th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Bloodflames by Nicolas Calas, 1947 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Inman Gallery (Box 3)
    - Catalogue of Works by the Late Henry Inman, 1846 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - International Art Center, 310 Riverside Drive, New York (Box 3)
    - Docks, Bridges, Waterways, of New York by Contemporary Artists of the Metropolitan Area, October 6-November 4, 1935 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: J-L, Series 4:
  - Jacques Seligmann & Co., 705 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Mr. Robert Reid Invites you to an Exhibition of his Portrait Impressions loaned by the Owners, opening February 15, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Portrait Drawings by Albert Sterner, April 3-15 [annotated 22], 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - James F. Drake, Inc., 4 W. 40th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Original Drawings and Water Colors by Modern Illustrators, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Kennedy & Co., 613 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Etchings and Dry Points by Dwight C. Sturges, October 16-November 11, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Mezzotnts by Max Rosenthal, May 1917 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Levon West - First Exhibition of Water Color Paintings, March 20-April 30, [1934?] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Kevorkians, 40 W. 57th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Hugo Gellert Exhibition, May 1-31, 1923 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Kingore Galleries, 24 E. 46th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Paintings by Curtis Moffat, April 30-May 10 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Kleemann-Thorman Galleries, 575 Madison Avenue, New York City (Box 3)
    - Six New Etchings by Walter Tittle, undated (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Etchings and Lithographs by Albert Sterner, undated (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Etchings and Etchings in Color by William Meyerowitz, March 4-18 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Knoedler's Gallery, 15 Old Bond Street (Box 3)
    - Exhibition of Sculpture of British Champion Animals by Herbert Haseltine, July 8-31, 1925 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Herbert Haseltine Exhibition of Sculpture, July 10-August 9, 1930 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - "The Lantern" Gallery/Tea Room, 164 W. 4th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Contemporary Group - "The Lantern" Exhibition, September 3-17 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - 2nd Contemporary Group - "The Lantern" Exhibition, September 18-October 3 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Leavitt Art Galleries, No. 817 Broadway (Box 3)
    - The Knoedler Collection: Modern Oil Paintings by Distinguished Foreign and American Artists, undated (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Liberal Club, 137 MacDougal St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Studio Tea and Art Exhibit by Emile Gruppe, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Library of Congress, Washington, D.C. (Box 3)
    - [Announcement] 6th Cabinet of American Illustration Original - Drawings by Edward Penfield, May 11, 1916 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Los Angeles Museum, Los Angeles, California (Box 3)
    - The Mr. and Mrs. William Preston Harrison Galleries of American Art, 1934 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Louis Katz Art Galleries, 103 W. 74th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Exhibition of Thumb Box Sketches by American Artists, December 2, 1915-January 8, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
- Art Exhibition Catalogs: M-O, Series 5:
  - M. A. McDonald, 665 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Reginald Marsh Prints and Drawings, February 13-March l, 1939 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - M. De Zayas, 549 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Chinese Paintings from the Collection of Charles Vignier, October 22-November 1, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - African Negro Sculpture, November 5-15, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Courbet, Manet, Degas, Renoir, Cezanne, Seurat, Matisse, November 7-December 6, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by John Covert, April 19-May 1, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Watercolors and Aqua-Tints by Arthur B. Davies, January 26-February 14, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Charles Sheeler, February 16-28, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Walt Kuhn, March 22-April 3, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - M. Knoedler & Co., 556-558 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Whimsical Dolls and Silhouettes by E. O. Hoppe, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Imaginative Paintings by Thirty Young Artists of New York City, April 2-16 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - American Painters, February 15-March 3 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Portraits and Flowers by Gladys Thayer, January 6-17 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - American Paintings and Sculpture Pertaining to the War, April 29-May 17 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by John S. Sargent and Edward D. Boit, March 16-30, 1912 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Recent Portraits by Albert Sterner, November 15-27, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Ninth Annual Summer Exhibition of Paintings by American Artists, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Nature-Camouflage Studies by Abbott H. Thayer, The Originator of Camouflage ("Concealing Coloration"), April 29-May 11, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by George O. Hart of New Orleans, Florida, and West Indies, October 10-27, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Eleventh Annual Summer Exhibition of Paintings by American Artists, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Recent Work by A Group of American Artists, with a forward by Frederick James Gregg, March 15-29, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Sculptured Work of Mrs. Clare Sheridan, March 21-April 2, 1921 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Recent Works by Bakst, December 6-16, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by Sargent and Barbazon, February 27-March 15, 1941 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - MacBeth Galleries and Gallery of William MacBeth, 450 5th Ave. and 237 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Water Colors by American Artists, December 7-21, 1892 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by American Artists, November 8-29, 1893 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Drawings in Water Colors and Black and White by C. R. Grant, and Wilson de Meza, December 2-16, 1893 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Landscapes by American Artists, April 13-May 6, 1894 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures and Sketches by Anton Mauve, March 15-30, 1895 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings in Oil by Philip Zilcken, February 17-29, 1896 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Arthur B. Davies, March 9-21, 1896 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Robert C. Minor, March 6-March 20, 1897 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Arthur B. Davies, April 24-May 8, 1897 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Expressions of New England Landscape by Leonard Ochtman, January 31-February 12, 1898 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Landscapes by A. H. Wyant and Homer D. Martin, March 14-26, 1898 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Charles Walter Stetson, February 17-March 9, 1899 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Painting and Sculpture by Women Artists for the Benefit of the Woman Suffrage Campaign, September 27-October 17 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Augustus Vincent Tack, November 11-23, 1907 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Jerome Myers, January 6-18, 1908 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Paintings by Arthur B. Davies, William J. Glackens, Robert Henri, Ernest Lawson, George Luks, Maurice B. Prendergast, Everett Shinn, John Sloan ["The Eight"], February 3-15, 1908 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Forty Selected Paintings by Living American Artists, February 19-March 7, 1908 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Forty Selected Paintings by Living American Artists, January 7-21, 1909 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Selected Paintings by American Artists from April 21, 1914 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Oil and Water Colors by Hayley Lever [and] Recent Paintings by Randall Davey, October 30-November 19, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Opening Exhibition of Our Second Quarter-Century, October 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Second Exhibition of "Intimate Paintings", December 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by John H. Twachtman, January 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Portraits and Landscapes by Gladys Thayer, March 22-April 11, 1921 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - MacDowell Club, 108 W. 55th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Paintings by Glenn O. Coleman, Stuart Davis, Henri de Mance, Rudolph Dirks, Henry J. Glintenkamp, Kathleen McEnery, Gus Mager, Sigurd Schow, November 30-December 12, 1911 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Eleanor Bayard, Mary Bayne Bugbird, Stewart Stroud Crise, Mark D. Dodd, Robert C. Doran, Adelaide J. Lawson, Richard L. Marwede, H. E. Schnakenberg, Hugo Von Schwanenfluegel, Frances M. Wintringham, February 16-24, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by H. A. Brewster, Charlotte B. Coman, Fanny Griswold Ely, E. Marguerite Enors, Ethel Evans, Anna Fisher, Georgiana Timkin Fry, Rhoda Holmes Nicholls, Clara Weaver Parrish, Edith Penman, Alethea H. Platt, E. N. Vanderpoel, March 16-24, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors, Pastels and Drawings by Four Groups of Artists, April 27-May 12, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Theresa F. Bernstein, Frederick K. Detwiller, George Pearse Ennis, Alice Judson, Oscar H. Julius, Victor A. Seydel, H. Vance Swope, James Wieland, November 7-19, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Belle Bennet, G.L. Berg, Arthur Edwin Bye, Adri de Groot, Ruth H. Hammerslough, Gertrude Fay Lothorp, Violet Mege, W. A. Patty, Bertrand Rasmussen, Roland Rood, November 26-December 8, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition of Sketches and Small Pictures by Four Groups of Artists, December 17-29, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Olaf N. Brauner, Elizabeth Curtis, Walter Farndon, Emily Nichols Hatch, Margaret W. Huntington, Bela Mayer, Ernest D. Roth, William Starkweather, January 7-19, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Caroline M. Bell, Lydia Floret, Sara M. Hess, Frances Keffer, A. Garfield Learnes, Clara Mamre Norton, Delos Palmer, Jr., L.J. Stone, Frances Hudson Storrs, Agnes Weinrich, Julia M. Wickham, Arthur Young, January 28-February 9, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Sculpture by Mary L. Alexander, Gifford Beal, Reynolds Beal, George Bellows, Clarence K. Chatterton, Bernhard Gussow, Robert Henri, Leon Kroll, Florence Mix, Rex Slinkard, John Sloan, Chalia Millett, February 18-March 2, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Sculpture by Karl Anderson, William J. Baer, Frederick C. Frieseke, Alexander Hudnut, Jonas Lie, Jane Peterson, Jane Poupelet, Janet Scudder, Lionel Walden, April 1-13, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors, Pastels and Drawings by Four Groups of Artists, April 22-May 11, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Madison Art Gallery, 305 Madison Avenue, New York City (Box 3)
    - Recent Paintings by Walt Kuhn, December 9 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Massachusetts Charitable Mechanic Association, Boston, Mass. (Box 3)
    - Fourteenth Exhibition, Department of Fine Arts, 1881 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Memorial Art Gallery, Rochester, N.Y. (Box 3)
    - Paintings by W. Elmer Schofield and an Exhibition of Paintings Representative of the Modern Movement in American Art, February 16-March 7, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 3)
    - Retrospective Exhibition of American Paintings, undated (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Loan Collection of Paintings and Sculpture, May-October, 1883 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Albert P. Ryder Memorial Exhibition, March 11-April 14, 1918 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - George Bellows Memorial Exhibition, October 12-November 1925 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - The Architect and the Industrial Arts, February 12-March 24, 1929 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Artists for Victory: An Exhibition of Contemporary American Art, 1942 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Milch Galleries, 108 W. 57th, New York City (Box 3)
    - Paintings by Jerome Myers, February 8-March 1 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Ossip L. Linde, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Works by Abbott H. Thayer Belonging to the Thayer Estate and Including Important Works Never Before Exhibited, December 5-31 [annotated "Extended to Jany 7"] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Etchings by William Meyerowitz, [1920?] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Wi11iam Meyerowitz Etchings and Color-Etchings, Forewards by Ellen Day Hale and Gabrielle DeV. Clements, October 29, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Etchings by William Meyerowitz, January 8-27 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - South Sea Island Impressions by Wm Ritschel, January 29-February 10 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings of California by William Ritschel, March 3-15 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Arthur C. Goodwin, February 14-26 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Robert Henri, February 25-March 16 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings of the Far East by Leon Gaspard, March 5-31 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Pastels by Henry C. White [includes announcement], December 26-January 13 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Lillian Genth, March 17-29, [annotated March 20-April 2] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - American Sculpture for the Town and Country House, the Garden and the Grounds, May 2-30 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Theresa F. Bernstein, November 1-15 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - The E. & A. Milch Gallery - Opening Exhibition, November 4-18, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Second Annual Exhibition by the Painter-Gravers of America, December 10-31, 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Annual Holiday Exhibition of Selected Paintings of Limited Size by American Artists, December 18, 1918-January 16, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Mary Prindeville, January 13-25, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Modern Gallery, 500 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Picabia Exhibition, January 5-25 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Water Colors and Drawings by Honore Daumier, Constantin Guys, and Henri De Toulouse-Lautrec, February 1-28 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Drawings & Etchings by Helene Perdriat, February 18-March 2 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Drawings and Water Colors by Marie Laurencin, undated (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors and Drawings, April 4-13, [1918] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - African Negro Sculpture, January 21-February 9, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Montclair Art Museum (Box 3)
    - Paintings Loaned by National Arts Club, New York [and] Portraits in Colored Wax by Ethel Frances Mundy, December 2, 1915-January 30, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Sculpture Pertaining to the Garden, May 1-June 9, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Sketches, September 28-November 3, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Montross Gallery, 372 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Eleventh Annual Exhibition - Ten American Painters, March 17-April 4, 1908 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Opening Exhibition Season 1914-1915, October 10-31, 1914 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Drawings, Etchings, Lithographs and Sculpture by Henri Matisse, January 20-February 27, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Henri Matisse Exhibition - Catalogue with Half-tone Reproductions and Color Plate, January 20-February 27, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures, Studies and Sketches by Horatio Walker, March 2-20, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings, Drawings and Sculpture, March 23-April 24, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition of Modern Art Applied to Decoration, April 28-May 22, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Pictures by Childe Hassam, November 27-December 11, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Max Weber, December 14-30, 1915 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Cezanne Exhibition, through January 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Fifty Pictures by Fifty Artists, February 8-March 4, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures by Jean Crotti, Marcel Duchamp, Albert Gleizes, Jean Metzinger, April 4-22, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - New York Society of Etchers, October 31-November 11, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Contemporary Group Exhibition, December 12-30, 1916 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures by Childe Hassam, January 4-20, 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Jonas Lie, January 30-February 10, 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition - Arthur B. Davies, Walt Kuhn, Jules Pascin, Charles Sheeler, Max Weber, February 13-March 3, 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Twentieth Annual Exhibition Ten American Painters [includes announcement], March 6-24, 1917 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - New Pictures by Randall Davey, April 2-13, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition of Pictures, January 4-25, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures by Gari Melchers, January 28-February 15, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures by Kenneth Hayes Miller, February 18-March 8, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Recent Pictures by Horatio Walker, March 11-29, 1919 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Gari Melchers - Figures and Landscapes, January 10-31, 1920 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Bryson Burroughs Paintings and Drawings, March 19-April 9, 1921 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Pictures by Allen Tucker, January 3-21, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors, Oil Paintings and Etchings [by] John Marin, January 24-February 11, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Pictures by Kenneth Hayes Miller - Invitation, February 14-March 4, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition - Contemporary Art, April, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings Adirondack Mountains and Persia by Harold F. Weston, November 8-25, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Indian Folk Lore Pictures Painted by F. Overton Colbert, Chickasaw Indian, January 5-20, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Max Kuehne, January 15-23, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Special Exhibition Contemporary Art, January 23-February 10, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Embroidered Tapestries by Marguerite Zorach, February 5-17, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Max Weber, February 12-March 3, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by Oliver Chaffee, October 29-November 10, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Allen Tucker, January 3-24, 1924 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Selected Works by Walt Kuhn [includes announcement], January 5-26, 1924 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by Robert Hallowell, November 4-25, 1925 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Carved-Painted Decorative Wood Panels by Elmer L. MacRae, March 15-27 [annotated "April 3rd"], 1926 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Mrs. Malcom's Gallery, 114 E. 66th, New York City (Box 3)
    - Drawings, Paintings and Sculpture by Beonne Boronda (Aged ten), January 30-February 11, [1921] (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Stewart Reinhart, May 2-16 [annotated 23], 1921 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by J. Lars Hoftrup, November 28-December 10 [annotated 17], 1921 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Etchings by Katharine Merrill, March 13-25, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Municipal Art Committee, New York (Box 3)
    - First Annual Report 1935, 1936 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Municipal Art Gallery, 40 Irving Pl., New York City (Box 3)
    - Association of Culture Ninth Annual Exhibition, January 14-February 26, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Association of Culture Tenth Annual Exhibition, January 14-February 20, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Contemporary American Art, June 19-October 1, 1929 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - Murray Hill Gallery, 274 Madison Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Max Weber, February 12-24 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 3)
    - Water Colors by American and European Artists, February 26-April 14, 1929 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Museum of Modern Art, Heckscher Bldg., 730 5th Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Exhibition of Early Modern Architecture, Chicago, 1870-1910, January 16-February 23, 1933 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - First Loan Exhibition - Cezanne, Gauguin, Seurat, Van Gogh, November 1929 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - [Brochure] First Loan Exhibition - Cezanne, Gauguin, Seurat, Van Gogh, November 8-December 7, 1929 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - Mussmann Gallery (Box 3)
    - Water Colors by Caroline Van H. Bean, January 12-31 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Water Colors by Philip Little, February 1-18 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings of the South by Margaret M. Law, March 18-April 1 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Manhattan Painters-Gravers' Club, November 13-27 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - National Academy of Design, 23rd Street and 4th Avenue, New York City (Box 3)
    - Critical Guide to the Exhibition at the National Academy of Design, 1859 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the 35th Annual Exhibition, 1860 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Ceremony of the Laying of the Corner Stone of the New Edifice, October 21, 1863 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Constitution of the National Academy of Design, 1865 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Catalogue of the Forty-First Annual Exhibition, 1866 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Eighty-Sixth Annual Exhibition, March 11-April 16, 1911 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Eighty-Seventh Annual Exhibition, March 9-April 14, 1912 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Winter Exhibition, December 14, 1912-January 12, 1913 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Centennial Exhibition, October 17-November 15, 1925 and December 1, 1925-January 3, 1926 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - National Arts Club, 119 E. 19th St., New York City (Box 3)
    - Exhibition: Contemporary Art, February 5-March 7, 1914 (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
    - Exhibition of Sculpture, April 7-30, 1915 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Exhibition of the Work of Painter and Sculptor Members, January 3-February 1, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Humorists' Exhibition, December 7-30, 1921 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Group Exhibition - Carl Rungius, F. Luis Mora, Edward C. Volkert, Edmund Graecen, Roy H. Brown, Oscar Fehrer, Eugene Higgins, Lee Lawrie, March 7-26, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors 1924 Auction, April 2-16, 1924 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - National Association of Women Painters and Sculptors (Box 3)
    - [Invitation-Private View] Twenty-Seventh Annual Exhibition 1918, April 8, 1918 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - 1922 Auction, March 15, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - 1923 Auction, April 23, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - National Gallery of Art (Box 3)
    - Paintings and Other Art Objects Exhibited on the Occasion of the Opening of the Gallery in the New Building of the United States National Museum, March 17, 1910 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
  - New Art Circle, 35 W. 57th, New York City (Box 3)
    - Artlover J. B. Neumann's Bilderhefte "This issue is a program of our New York Exhibitions...,", undated (Box 3, Reel unfilmed)
  - New Gallery, 600 Madison Ave., New York City (Box 3)
    - Group Exhibition of Paintings by Ernest Fiene, Arnold Friedman, Leon Hartl, Joseph Stella, Carl Sprinchorn, March 5-31 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - The Hundred Dollar Holiday Exhibitio n [announcement included], December 12-January 2 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Catalogue First Exhibition, opening Nov. 14, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings by James Chapin, February 6-20, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Paintings and Drawings by Boris Grigoriev, April 6-28, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - First Exhibition of Drawings of Benjamin Greenstein, February 6-17, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)
    - Opening of the Second Season, October 26, 1923 (Box 3, Reel 4859)